<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pgum thinking space</title>
    <description>My interpretation of reality</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Workplace checklist</title>
        <description>
          
          Workplace checklist

[ ] Asdf 1 
[ ] Asdf 2 
[ ] Asdf 3

        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/checklists/workplace_checklist/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/checklists/workplace_checklist/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Teams vision of goal</title>
        <description>
          This is where I will tell my friends way too much about me - 
          Goals Team identifies “ideal” vision Team asserts current state Team defines steps toward “ideal” state Time and place Around 1 hour long Room to sit in circle Participants Group of interest Moderator Prerequisites Team members have defined team goals Team members understand requirements for empirical process Room and items needed...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/scenarios/vision_of_goal/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/scenarios/vision_of_goal/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Turning grumble into actions</title>
        <description>
          This is where I will tell my friends way too much about me - 
          Goals Group understand negative effects of grumble Group can identify underlaying needs from current work Group assign working groups or individuals to most important actions identified Time and place Around 1 hour long Room to sit in circle Participants Group of interest Moderator Prerequisites Group members know each other fairly...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/scenarios/turning_grumble_into_actions/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/scenarios/turning_grumble_into_actions/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opportunities_and_challenges</title>
        <description>
          
          Opportunities and challenges Goals Identification Team and new SM both define potential opportunities and challenges ahead Defining clear rules and values from the start of cooperation in new team Team identifies areas they treat as important Fresh start with health attitude Participants The Team Scrum Master Prerequisites Room and items...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/opportunities_and_challenges/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/opportunities_and_challenges/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fishbowl</title>
        <description>
          
          Fishbowl Goals Deep-dive into selected topic of high importance by group of interest Well defined list of expectations Vision of desired outcome Enabling all participants to voice their opinions over key topics Deepens participants observation skills Participants Group of interest Moderator Scrum Master Prerequisites Before start refresh relevant knowledge among...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/fishbowl/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/fishbowl/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>End_the_sentence</title>
        <description>
          
          
End the sentence

        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/end_the_sentence/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/end_the_sentence/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You_dont_care_about_it_if_you_dont_measure_it</title>
        <description>
          
          You don’t care about it if you don’t measure it Description Word measure can be substituted with: notice, speak about, rise up, etc. Without benchmarking there is no possible way to make rational decision. If problems aren’t noticed, or spoken about there is no way to react. Purpose Small set...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/you_dont_care_about_it_if_you_dont_measure_it/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/you_dont_care_about_it_if_you_dont_measure_it/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Maieutics</title>
        <description>
          
          Maieutics - Socratic method #2 gr. μαιευτικός maieutikhos It is named after the Classical Greek philosopher Socrates and is introduced by him in Plato’s Theaetetus as midwifery (maieutics) because it is employed to bring out definitions implicit in the interlocutors’ beliefs, or to help them further their understanding. 1 It’s...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/maieutics/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/maieutics/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>8 wastes od manufacturing - DOWNTIME</title>
        <description>
          This is where I will tell my friends way too much about me - 
          Downtime is the consequence of waste Its also acronym for 8 types of waste as defined by lean management. In IT some kinds of waste is hard to observe and measure as we don’t produce physical objects. Defects: How many times client says “It’s not working” or “It’s not what...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/concepts/downtime_8wastes/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/concepts/downtime_8wastes/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
